<?xml version="1.0"?>
<information>
	<book>
            <id>95</id>
            <title>Our Great Big Backyard</title>
            <isbn>0062468359</isbn>
            <authors> Laura Bush,Jenna Bush Hager</authors>
            <publisher>HarperCollins</publisher>
            <releaseDate>2016-05-10</releaseDate>
            <pageCount>40</pageCount>
            <categories>Juvenile Fiction</categories>
            <description>To help commemorate the one hundredth anniversary of the National Park Service, #1 New York Times bestselling authors former First Lady Laura Bush and her daughter Jenna Bush Hager have created an exuberant picture book tribute to our national parks and the importance and fun of connecting with nature. Our Great Big Backyard follows Jane, whose plans of spending the summer playing video games with her friends are dashed when her parents announce that her family is going on a road trip to national parks around the country. Yet somewhere between the Everglades and Big Bend National Park, things begin to change. Jane starts paying attention to the magnificent sights and spends less time looking at her screen. The stunning views open up her imagination as she and her brother see everything that nature has to offer. And the more Jane discovers, the more she realizes how much there is to love about the outdoors—whether she’s in a national park across the country or right in her own backyard.
            </description>
            <totalCopies>5</totalCopies>
            <availableCopies>5</availableCopies>
            <imageURL>http://books.google.com/books/content?id=e6GcjgEACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api</imageURL>
            <type>0</type>
	</book>
        
        <book>
            <id>96</id>
            <title>For One More Day</title>
            <isbn>1401309577</isbn>
            <authors>Mitch Albom</authors>
            <publisher>Hyperion</publisher>
            <releaseDate>2008-04-01</releaseDate>
            <pageCount>208</pageCount>
            <categories>Fiction</categories>
            <description>From the author of The Five People You Meet in Heaven and Tuesdays with Morrie, a new novel that millions of fans have been waiting for. \"Every family is a ghost story . . .\" Mitch Albom mesmerized readers around the world with his number one New York Times bestsellers, The Five People You Meet in Heaven and Tuesdays with Morrie. Now he returns with a beautiful, haunting novel about the family we love and the chances we miss. For One More Day is the story of a mother and a son, and a relationship that covers a lifetime and beyond. It explores the question: What would you do if you could spend one more day with a lost loved one As a child, Charley \"Chick\" Benetto was told by his father, \"You can be a mama's boy or a daddy's boy, but you can't be both.\" So he chooses his father, only to see the man disappear when Charley is on the verge of adolescence. Decades later, Charley is a broken man. His life has been crumbled by alcohol and regret. He loses his job. He leaves his family. He hits bottom after discovering his only daughter has shut him out of her wedding. And he decides to take his own life. He makes a midnight ride to his small hometown, with plans to do himself in. But upon failing even to do that, he staggers back to his old house, only to make an astonishing discovery. His mother--who died eight years earlier-is still living there, and welcomes him home as if nothing ever happened. What follows is the one \"ordinary\" day so many of us yearn for, a chance to make good with a lost parent, to explain the family secrets, and to seek forgiveness. Somewhere between this life and the next, Charley learns the astonishing things he never knew about his mother and her sacrifices. And he tries, with her tender guidance, to put the crumbled pieces of his life back together. Through Albom's inspiring characters and masterful storytelling, readers will newly appreciate those whom they love--and may have thought they'd lost--in their own lives. For One More Day is a book for anyone in a family, and will be cherished by Albom's millions of fans worldwide.
            </description>
            <totalCopies>8</totalCopies>
            <availableCopies>8</availableCopies>
            <imageURL>http://books.google.com/books/content?id=SdRFPgAACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api</imageURL>
            <type>0</type>
	</book>
        
        
        
        
</information>